Guide to the Rice University Football programs collection, 1913-2018 UA 223
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: 1970-2011, 231474
  - Rice vs. SMU, November 10, 1984; 231560 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. Miami, September 14, 1985; 231559 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Lamar, September 28, 1985; 231558 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 12, 1985; 231557 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, October 26, 1985; 231556 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 2, 1985; 231555 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Rice vs. SMU, September 13, 1986; 231554 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - TCU vs. Rice, October 11, 1986; 231553 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 18, 1986; 231552 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, October 25, 1986; 231551 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, November 1, 1986; 231550 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 15, 1986; 231549 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. Air Force, November 22, 1986; 231548 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Lamar, September 5, 1987; 231547 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Indiana vs. Rice, September 12, 1987; 231546 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - LSU vs. Rice, September 19, 1987; 231545 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. Southwest Texas State, September 26, 1987; 231544 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 3, 1987; 231543 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 10, 1987; 231542 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, October 17, 1987; 231541 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, October 24, 1987; 231540 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, October 31, 1987; 231539 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, November 28, 1987; 231538 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Rice vs. Indiana, September 10, 1988; 231537 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 1, 1988; 231536 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 15, 1988; 231535 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, October 22, 1988; 231534 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, October 29, 1988; 231533 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Notre Dame vs. Rice, November 5, 1988; 231532 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 12, 1988; 231531 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. North Texas, November 19, 1988; 231530 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. SW Louisiana, September 23, 1989; 231529 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 14, 1989; 231528 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, October 28, 1989; 231527 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 4, 1989; 231526 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. Wake Forest, September 1, 1990; 231525 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, September 8, 1990; 231524 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. Northwestern, September 22, 1990; 231523 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 6, 1990; 231522 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - TCU vs. Rice, October 13, 1990; 231521 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 20, 1990; 231520 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, October 27, 1990; 231519 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, November 3, 1990; 231518 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Rice vs. Southern Methodist, 1990-11-10 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Ohio State vs. Rice, September 4, 1993; 231517 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, September 11, 1993; 231516 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Rice vs. Sam Houston State, September 18, 1993; 231515 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. Iowa State, September 25, 1993; 231514 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 2, 1993; 231513 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 9, 1993; 231512 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Iowa State vs. Rice, September 24, 1994; 231511 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, September 10, 1994; 231510 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. Kansas State, September 17, 1994; 231509 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 8, 1994; 231508 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 15, 1994; 231507 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, October 22, 1994; 231506 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - TCU vs. Rice, October 29, 1994; 231505; (misprinted October 8 on cover) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. SMU, November 5, 1994; 231504 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 12, 1994; 231503 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. Navy, 1994-11-19 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - University of Houston vs. Rice, November 26, 1994; 231502 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rice vs. UNLV, September 2, 1995; 231501 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, September 16, 1995; 231500 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - LSU vs. Rice, September 23, 1995; 231499 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Army vs. Rice, September 30, 1995; 231498 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 14, 1995; 231497 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 21, 1995; 231496 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 9, 1995; 231495 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston (2 copies), December 2, 1995; 231494 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. Kansas State, September 21, 1996; 231493 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 19, 1996; 231492 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. Utah, November 2, 1996; 231491 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. Tulsa, November 23, 1996; 231490 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. Air Force, 1997-09-06 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 8, 1997; 231489 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. UTEP, November 22, 1997; 231488 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. SMU, September 5, 1998; 231487 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. Northwestern, September 19, 1998; 231486 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. Tulsa, October 17, 1998; 231485 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - University of Houston vs. Rice, September 4, 1999; 231484 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. Navy, October 10, 2009; 231475 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Rice vs. San Jose State, October 16, 1999; 231483 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 23, 1999; 231482 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Rice vs. UTEP, November 13, 1999; 231481 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, September 2, 2000; 231480 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. Hawaii, October 21, 2000; 231479 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. SMU, November 4, 2000; 231478 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, 2005-11-12 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. Houston, 2006-09-02 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. University of AL Birmingham, 2006-10-17 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. East California, 2006-11-18 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. SMU, 2006-11-25 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, 2007-09-15 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. Memphis, 2007-10-20 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. UTEP, 2007-11-03 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. North Texas, 2008-09-27 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. Southern MS, 2008-10-18 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. Army, 2008-11-08 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Rice vs. Marshall, 2008-11-22 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, November 29, 2008; 231477 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Rice vs. Vanderbilt, September 26, 2009; 231476 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Rice vs. Tulsa, 2009-10-03 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. Navy, 2009-10-10 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. UCF, 2009-10-24 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, 2009-11-14 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. UTEP, 2010-09-18 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. Northwestern, 2010-09-18 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, 2010-09-25 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Rice vs. SMU, 2010-10-02 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Rice vs. Houston, 2010-10-16 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Tulane vs. Rice, 2010-11-13 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Rice vs. East Carolina, 2010-11-20 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Texas vs. Rice, 2011-09-03 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Rice vs. Purdue, 2011-09-10 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Rice vs. Memphis, 2011-10-08 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Rice vs. Tulsa, 2011-10-22 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Rice vs. UTEP, 2011-11-05 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, 2011-11-19 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Series III: 2013-2018
  - Rice vs. Kansas, September 14, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. Florida Atlantic, September 28, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. UTEP, October 26, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. LA Tech, November 16, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, November 30, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. Notre Dame, August 30, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Hawaii vs. Rice, 2014-10-04 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - North Texas vs. Rice, 2014-10-25 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. Marshall, 2014-11-15 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - UTEP vs. Rice, 2014-11-21 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. Wagner, September 5, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - UTSA vs. Rice, 2015-09-21 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Baylor vs. Rice, September 26, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Rice vs. Western Kentucky, October 3, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Rice vs. Army, October 24, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. Louisiana Tech, October 30, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Southern Mississippi, November 14, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Rice vs. Charlotte, November 28, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, 2016-09-16 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. Prairie View A&M, 2016-10-22 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Stanford vs. Rice, 2017-08-27 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Rice vs. Prairie View A&M, 2018 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Covers only, various years (Box 17)